Dr. Sumiya Mushtaq

House # 13/15-A-11, Nishtar Park,

Islam Nagar, Walton Road, Lahore Cantt.

E.mail: drsumiyamushtaq28@gmail.com

Contact # 03226415168

Respected Sir / Madam,

I am a skilled professional of 'Regulatory Affairs' with comprehensive knowledge & experience of preparing product registration dossiers for international territories.

With experience in preparing company & product registration dossiers for Senegal, Mongolia, Kenya, Sri Lanka, Cambodia, Myanmar, Philippines, Uganda, Ghana, Afghanistan, Kyrgyzstan & Nigeria etc in CTD/ACTD format; I grew up with a good communication & management skills in regulatory affairs that are particularly effective for the business enrichment internationally.

Along-with the regulatory matters of exporting countries, I am also looking after the registration of imported products & medical devices etc with DRAP.

Apart from that; I have experience of technical documentation. This could be an added advantage for this profession. Details of my qualifications are in the enclosed C.V.

I believe that my knowledge & capabilities will enable me to excel in your esteemed organization. I am looking forward to meet u as soon as I am considered to further discuss my qualifications and experience.

Thank you for your consideration.

Sincerely,

Dr. Sumiya Mushtaq

#### **OBJECTIVE:**

I want to be part of the success in an environment of growth and excellence.

## **EXPERIENCE:**

## **\*** FEROZSONS LABORATORIES LIMITED

## Nov 2014 - till date

## > Promoted to Senior Executive Regulatory Affairs

- Preparation of Product Dossiers for Exporting Countries according to their guidelines
- Working on registration of imported products and medical devices with DRAP
- Answer the queries or provision of all additional documents
- Coordination with other relevant departments
- Arrangement of registration samples and NOC
- Attestation of legal documents through field officer
- Art Work Proof Reading
- Maintenance of Data Bank

## > Joined As Executive Assistant Regulatory Affairs

• The responsibilities were same as above.

#### \* ENGLISH PHARMACEUTICAL INDUSTRIES

## May 2014 - Nov 2014

#### > As Assistant Product Manager

- Training of Marketing Field Staff
- Preparation of Product Manuals
- Art Work Proof Reading
- Look after all matters regarding marketing
- Tracking Field Staff through documentation
- Preparation of Local Dossiers
- Assist Manager Regulatory Affairs in preparing Export Dossiers

# \* MASS PHARMA (PVT).LTD

# February 2013 - March 2014

## **→** As Quality Control Analyst

- HPLC,U.V and FTIR operator
- Chemical Testing from Raw Material to Finished Product
- Stability studies
- Preparation of SOPs
- Preparation of COAs

## **INTERNSHIPS:**

- \* THE CHILDREN HOSPITAL AND THE INSTITUTE OF CHILD HEALTH
- \* ENGLISH PHARMACEUTICAL INDUSTRIES

# **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION:**

Pharm .D

University of Lahore (2008-2013)

F.Sc (Pre-Medical)

Govt. College for Women, Gulberg, Lahore (2005-2007)

<u>Matric</u>

Qurban Public Girls Higher Secondary School (2003-2005)

## **EXPERTIES:**

- Effective communication
- Keen study and filtration of product registration guidelines
- Searching clinical studies on safety and efficacy of molecules
- Thorough review of dossier to make it correct and true
- Good command on Microsoft Office
- Attended training course on CTD preparation
- Good command over Q.C instruments handling and documentation

## PERSONAL INFORMATION:

Father's Name: Ch. Mushtaq Ahmad

DOB: 28th September, 1988.

Religion: Islam. Nationality: Pakistani. Marital status: Single

## **REFERENCES:**

Will be furnished on demand.